Hello and welcome to this course
您好，欢迎参加此课程
on Kotlin advanced programming.
在Kotlin Advanced编程中。
As an aspiring developer,
作为有抱负的开发商
you may have some existing knowledge
你可能有一些 现有知识
and skills in Android app development.
和Android的技能 应用程序开发。
This course will help you
本课程将帮助您
advance your app development level by
推进您的应用程序 发展水平
introducing you to the finer points
向您介绍 更好的点
of Kotlin code and concepts,
Kotlin代码和概念，
you will probably agree that
您可能会同意
there's an app for everything.
所有内容都有一个应用程序。
However, it's important to realize that
但是，这很重要 意识到这一点
there isn't a great app for everything.
没有很好的 应用程序的应用。
The all-important metric of user experience is
最重要的指标 用户体验是
determined by excellent design
由出色的设计决定
coupled with solid software development.
与实心结合 软件开发。
To achieve such excellence,
为了取得如此卓越的成就，
it's vital to continually grow
不断成长至关重要
your mastery of the Kotlin programming language.
您对Kotlin的掌握 编程语言。
In this advanced programming in Kotlin course,
在这个高级编程中 在科特林课程中，
you will expand your Kotlin
您将扩展您的Kotlin
programming knowledge so that you can
编程知识 这样你就可以
engineer better solutions when building Android apps.
工程师更好的解决方案 构建Android应用程序时。
Kotlin is an open-source language with
Kotlin是一个开源 语言
an Apache 2 license and is available free of charge.
Apache 2许可证，是 免费提供。
It is used daily and worldwide by
每天使用 和全球
large and small organizations
大小组织
to produce many different types of apps.
生产许多 不同类型的应用程序。
To do advanced app development work with Kotlin,
进行高级应用 Kotlin的开发工作，
you should have a good working knowledge
你应该有一个好 工作知识
of programming fundamentals.
编程基本面。
Be familiar with the concepts of
熟悉
user experience and user interface design,
用户体验和 用户界面设计，
and be able to create user interfaces in
并能够创建 用户界面中
Android Studio to assist with your learning,
Android Studio协助 随着你的学习，
you will view and work on
您将查看和工作
development tasks for the fictitious Restaurant,
开发任务 虚拟餐厅，
Little Lemon, where you will encounter
小柠檬，哪里 你会遇到的
many real-world scenarios with
许多真实的场景
your newly upscaled Kotlin knowledge,
您的新升级 Kotlin知识，
you will work through these scenarios,
你会努力 这些场景，
overcoming challenges and implementing solutions.
克服挑战和 实施解决方案。
As your skill set grows,
随着您的技能的增长，
you will focus on many Kotlin language tools,
您将专注于许多 Kotlin语言工具，
why you need them and how they are used.
为什么您需要它们 它们的使用方式。
In this course introduction,
在本课程中，
you may encounter some new terms,
您可能会遇到 一些新术语，
but don't worry if you don't
但是不用担心你不
fully understand all of them.
充分了解所有这些。
During the course, you'll explore
在过程中， 您将探索
these concepts in more detail
这些概念更详细
along with the core skills that are
与核心 技能是
required during app development with Kotlin.
在应用过程中需要 Kotlin的发展。
This course consists of four weeks of learning.
本课程包括 学习四个星期。
By the end of this course,
到本课程结束时，
you should have acquired the skills and knowledge with
您应该已经获得了 技能和知识与
the necessary tools to complete
完成的必要工具
the end-of-course Android project.
课程结束 Android项目。
Let's break down the content you will cover in
让我们分解 您将介绍的内容
each week of this advanced programming in Kotlin course.
这个高级的每个星期 Kotlin课程的编程。
Week 1 covers the key features of
第1周涵盖 关键特征
Kotlin and Android and how they interact.
Kotlin和Android和 他们如何互动。
After your studies this week,
本周学习后，
you will be able to explain how to use
你将能够 说明如何使用
inheritance to decide how a component should behave.
继承决定如何 组件应行为。
Implement an application with an activity,
实施一个应用程序 在活动中，
implement a list adapter,
实现列表适配器，
and declare an object in Android.
并声明 对象在Android中。
Create a new static inner classes
创建一个新的静态 内部类
and inner modifiers when appropriate,
和内部修饰符 在适当的时候，
set and read activity arguments,
设置并读取活动参数，
and implement a companion object
并实现伴侣对象
with constant values and arguments.
具有恒定值 和争论。
Week 2 explores advanced object-oriented features.
第2周探索高级 面向对象的功能。
You will advance your skills
你会提高自己的技能
during this week to be able to
在这一周能够
use an extension function to add
使用扩展功能添加
a method to a class when appropriate.
班级的方法 在适当的时候。
Explain a testing methodology
解释测试方法
called test-driven development,
称为测试驱动的发展，
lists the main features of
列出
test-driven development or TDD,
测试驱动的开发或TDD，
and explain the purpose and types of testing.
并解释目的 和测试类型。
Use mocks and fakes for unit testing in Android,
使用模拟和假货 在Android中测试，
and define and use a generic class to solve a problem.
并定义和使用通用 解决问题的课程。
Week 3 covers functional programming.
第3周封面 功能编程。
You'll cover what it is and why it's useful?
你会涵盖什么 为什么有用？
In addition, you'll work with functions in Kotlin.
此外，您将工作 在Kotlin中具有功能。
After successfully completing this week,
成功 本周完成，
you'll be able to explain what
您可以解释什么
functional programming is and why it's useful.
功能编程 是以及为什么有用。
Read and define a function type.
读取并定义函数类型。
Use a lambda expression to define a function as
使用lambda表达式 将功能定义为
an object and define
一个物体并定义
a function that takes a function as an argument.
采用一个功能 作为一个参数。
Use collection processing functions
使用集合 处理功能
to process collections in
处理收集
different ways and use
不同的方式和使用
collection processing methods from
收集处理 方法
multi-step collection processing.
多步收集 加工。
In this final week,
在最后一周，
you will complete a practical development task,
您将完成一个 实际发展任务，
which will synthesize the concepts
它将合成 概念
and skills from this course to
和从本课程到的技能
create a list with filtering and
使用过滤创建一个列表，并
sorting in the final app development project,
在最终应用中排序 开发项目，
and allow you to reflect on
并让您反思
the next steps in the learning journey.
下一步 学习旅程。
The advanced programming in Kotlin course
高级编程 在Kotlin课程中
introduces you to many software engineering concepts.
向您介绍许多 软件工程概念。
These will help you to build a better Android app.
这些将帮助您 构建一个更好的Android应用程序。
Engineering excellence is not
卓越工程不是
simply about what works well on the surface,
只是关于什么有效 在地面上，
but also about everything that is happening within.
但也与一切 这正在发生。
Your programming skills and
您的编程技能和
approach to creating code solutions are
创建方法 代码解决方案是
the most important success factors
最重要的 成功因素
when it comes to app development.
到那个时刻 应用程序开发。
I look forward to helping you build
我很期待 帮助您建造
the advanced programming skills you
高级 编程技能
need to get to the next level.
需要达到一个新的水平。
Wishing you all the best on your Kotlin learning journey.
祝你一切顺利 您的Kotlin学习旅程。